unos.com 2019-10-01

# Uno Pizzeria & Grill: Privacy Policy

### Uno Restaurant Holdings Corporation  
Website Privacy Policy

Last Revised: April 18, 2019

#### General

Uno Restaurant Holdings Corporation (referred in this Privacy Policy as the "Company") respects the privacy of every individual who visits our websites. This Privacy Policy ("Policy") outlines the information the Company may collect from visitors to our websites hosted in the United States and how we may use and disclose that information.

We encourage you to read this Policy before using any of our websites. Your use of a website of the Company signifies that you agree with all terms of this Policy. Please do not use our websites if you disagree with any part of this Policy. 

#### What personal information do we collect and why do we collect it?

The Company may collect personal information about you (such as your name, postal address, telephone number, date of birth, company name and email address) that you provide voluntarily. You ordinarily are not required to register or provide personal information in order to access our websites, although certain sections of our websites may require registration. In addition, if you choose to contact us to ask a question we will collect your personal information so that we can respond to your question.

The Company may collect personal information online for all legal purposes, which include, but are not limited to:

**On-line Surveys**  
The Company conducts on-line surveys and other activities that may require online registration. Persons wishing to participate in those activities are asked to provide certain personal information. Some of the information requested for this purpose is optional, but other information, such as email address, is mandatory because it will be needed distribute promotions (such as coupons). Also, some activities may require the selection of a user ID and password by the participating individual. 

**"Contact" and Comment Features**  
The Company encourages visitors to its websites to contact us with questions and comments. Email addresses and other information of persons using these features may be collected in order to facilitate our responses to those inquiries.

**Purchases of Company Products**  
The unos.com website and other Company websites may offer individuals the opportunity to purchase products online. In connection with those purchases, customers may be asked to submit personal information, name, address, telephone number and email address, that is required to complete the transaction. 

**Special Promotions and Product Information**  
The Company also may offer you the opportunity to provide you with email updates and announcements concerning our products and special promotions. Personal information you have provided to the Company may be used to facilitate those communications.

#### When do we disclose the personal information we collect?

Except as provided herein, the Company will not sell, rent or otherwise disclose personal information about you to unaffiliated third parties.

We may disclose personal information you have provided through our websites to persons, or companies, that we retain to carry out promotions and other activities on our behalf. We also will disclose personal information if required by law, including compliance with warrants, subpoenas or other legal process.

The Company requires persons and companies to which it discloses personal information to restrict their use of such information to the purposes for which it has been provided by the Company, and not to disclose that information to others. The Company cannot be responsible, however, for any damages caused by the failure of unaffiliated third parties to honor their privacy obligations to the Company. Similarly, the Company is not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of other websites that are linked to our websites.

In addition to these limited disclosures of personal information, the Company may provide its affiliates or unaffiliated third parties with aggregate information about visitors to our sites. For example, we might disclose the median ages of visitors to our websites, or the numbers of visitors to our websites that come from different geographic areas. Such aggregate information will not include information of any individual visitors to our websites. 

The Company may provide personal and other information to a purchaser or successor entity in connection with the sale of the Company, a subsidiary or line of business associated with the Company, or substantially all of the assets of the Company or one of its subsidiaries, affiliates or lines of business. 

#### Special Note for Parents

The Company takes seriously its obligations under the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act concerning the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13. The Company's websites are not targeted to children. The Company does not knowingly accept personal information from children under the age of 13.

Parents should be aware that information that is voluntarily given by children or others in chat sessions, email exchanges, bulletin boards or the like may be used by other parties to generate unsolicited email or other contacts. The Company encourages all parents to instruct their children in the safe and responsible use of the Internet. 

#### How do we protect your personal information?

The Company takes measures to prevent unauthorized intrusion to its websites and the alteration, acquisition or misuse of personal information by unauthorized persons. However, the Company cautions visitors to its websites that no network, including the Internet, is entirely secure. 

#### What other information do we collect?

When you access and interact with one of our websites, we may collect certain information often referred to as "clickstream data." Such data may include the type of Internet browser and operating system you are using, the pages and information you accessed on our site, the total time spent on our site, and the domain name of the website from which you linked to our site. Also, where you have previously identified yourself in the registration process as affiliated with a particular business or organization, we may record the fact that a representative of your business or organization visited the site, along with other clickstream data concerning that visit. Clickstream data will not be used to identify you personally and will not be associated or correlated with any site visitor in a personally-identifiable manner.

#### Information placed automatically on your computer -- Cookies

When you view one of our websites, we may store certain information on your computer. This information may be in the form of a small text file called a "cookie" and can help us improve your experience with our websites in many ways. For example, cookies allow us to tailor a website to better match your interests and preferences. Notably, our websites use cookies to help understand which parts of our websites are most popular, where our visitors are going and how much time they spend there. Cookies are read only by the server that placed them, and are unable to execute any code or virus.

Also, where specific programs associated with our websites require a user ID and password, you have the option of requesting that we save your user ID and password so that you will not have to re-enter that information the next time you access the website. This function is accomplished by the placement of a cookie.

With most Internet browsers, you can erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. Please refer to your browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions. Please be aware, however, that some features and programs of our websites may be unavailable to you if cookies are erased or blocked. 

Some uses of cookies in connection with our websites may be under the control of unaffiliated entities that the Company retains for the management of certain programs and fulfillment of specific visitor/customer requests. The Company requires these entities to confine their use of cookies to the uses permitted by this Policy, but the Company cannot be responsible for third party uses of cookies.

#### Location Information

This site uses location data provided by your web browser if allowed. If you GPS location cannot be determined then your IP address is used to locate you. This information is not stored by UNO in any way. Location data is collected for the purpose of assigning your closest physical restaurant location to customize the web experience. Location data is not required to use or access this website.

#### Offline v. Online Practices

This Policy applies solely to the Company's information-gathering and dissemination practices in connection with its websites in the United States, and does not apply to any of our practices conducted offline or outside of the United States.

#### Changes to this Policy

This Policy is the sole authorized statement of the Company's practices with respect to the collection of personal information through the Company's websites and the subsequent use and disclosure of such information. Certain third party websites may be linked to the Company website. These third party websites include their own privacy policies. Please refer to these policies when using one of the linked websites.

The Company may revise this Policy from time to time. You should bookmark and periodically review this page to ensure that you are familiar with the most current version of this Policy. You can determine when this Policy was last revised by checking the "Last Revised" legend at the top of the Policy.

#### Contact

Uno Restaurant Holdings Corporation  
100 Charles Park Road  
Boston, MA 02132  

##### Eat, Drink & be happy for Hours.

##### Shareable  
Appetizers

### In the Bar  
All Day, Every Day

##### Rotating Taps

### National, Regional  
& Local Craft Beers

#####    
Classic Margarita

### Another Reason  
To visit bar Uno

Sign up now for exclusive savings, invites and the latest news sent straight to your inbox - starting with a **FREE APPETIZER** * welcome gift.

Become an Insider

*With purchase of entree. Offer only for new eClub subscribers.
